

STEPHANIE CALDWELL

DESIGNER/DEVELOPER

1780 Caneyville Rd.,

Morgantown, Kentucky
t: 1-270-361-1345
stephcaldwell97@gmail.com
github: @stephcaldwell
LinkedIn: @ steph-caldwell

CSS

HTML5

Bootstrap

Git/Terminal

WHOIAM

Beyond my legendary puzzle solving skills, I'm an experienced front end website designer and junior web developer with award-winning design skills. I'm passionate about improving the customer experience and in-house productivity, but above all, I understand that design and development is serious business.

EXPERIENCE

Morgantown, KY GIGGLE STICKS Design and shipping of wooden signs.		2020 - PRESENT
Owensboro, KY PAXTON MEDIA Copy Editor - Designed press-ready pages for multiple publications.		2019-2020
Nashville, TN FOCUS PRESS Responsible for pagination of books. Researched and implimented social media and advertising graphics.		2018-2019
Columbia, KY THE ADAIR PROGRESS Composition Manager - Responsible for layout and design of 3 weekly publications as well as training departmental staff.		2017-2018
EDUCATION		
BC Skills Academy Glasgow, Ky Coursework in HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Chrome Dev Tools, React, Git and Terminal.		2020
EXPERTISE		
WordPress	Adobe Photoshop	

Adobe InDesign

Microsoft Suite

WHM/CPanel

JavaScript